Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Maid=
=الخادمة=
=Episode 25=
=الحلقة 25=
Take it easy, Master Zhao.
خذ الأمر ببساطة، يا سيد تشاو.
I'll entrust Zhao to you.
سأسلم تشاو إليك.
Your Highness, what do you mean?
صاحب السمو ماذا تقصد؟
Though I don't know His Highness's plan,
على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف خطة سموه،
I can't abandon him.
لا أستطيع أن أتركه.
Your scheme
مخططك
never included him.
لم أدرجه أبدًا.
Why do you
لماذا تفعل ذلك؟
act this way now?
التصرف بهذه الطريقة الآن؟
I've always been his blade.
لقد كنت دائما شفرته.
I should face this with him.
ينبغي لي أن أواجه هذا معه.
Mother.
الأم.
Go, go!
إذهب، إذهب!
(He wants to protect you, the young master,)
(إنه يريد حمايتك أيها السيد الشاب)
(and this realm,)
(وهذه المملكة)
(yet never himself.)
(ولكن لم يكن نفسه أبدًا.)
(These guards will serve him with their lives.)
(هؤلاء الحراس سوف يخدمونه بحياتهم.)
(Take them with you.)
(خذهم معك.)
(You may break the siege for him.)
(يمكنك كسر الحصار عنه.)
(Pei Ji, you liar.)
(باي جي، أنت كاذب.)
(You must wait for me.)
(يجب عليك أن تنتظرني.)
M-Mother.
م-الأم.
Stop crying.
توقف عن البكاء.
Watch closely.
شاهد عن كثب.
Let them
دعهم
fight to the death.
القتال حتى الموت.
Only then can we
حينها فقط يمكننا
secure the throne.
تأمين العرش.
Kill him!
اقتله!
Kill him now!
اقتله الآن!
Even if you leave here,
حتى لو غادرت هنا،
you won't survive.
لن تنجو.
I never planned to leave.
لم أخطط للمغادرة أبدًا.
Nor will you!
ولن تفعل ذلك!
Pei Ji! Pei Ji!
باي جي! باي جي!
Xiyan.
شييان.
Xiyan!
مرحبًا!
Pei Ji!
باي جي!
The Western Army has fallen.
لقد سقط الجيش الغربي.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Don't come in!
لا تدخل!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
By my command,
بأمري،
no one
لا احد
shall enter the main hall!
سوف يدخل القاعة الرئيسية!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Pei Ji,
باي جي,
I want the people
أريد الناس
to live in peace.
للعيش بسلام.
I want the court
أريد المحكمة
to be just and harmonious.
أن تكون عادلة ومتناغمة.
I want this world
أريد هذا العالم
to know lasting tranquility.
لمعرفة الهدوء الدائم.
Pei Ji!
باي جي!
Pei Ji, open the door!
بي جي، افتح الباب!
P-Pei Ji!
ف-بي جي!
Prince Regent.
الأمير ريجنت.
You...
أنت...
Don't kill me.
لا تقتلني.
Don't you want the throne?
ألا تريد العرش؟
I'll have His Majesty decree
سأطلب من جلالته أن يصدر مرسومًا
t-to abdicate in your favor.
ت-التنازل عن العرش لصالحك.
When did I ever care
متى كنت أهتم؟
about the throne?
عن العرش؟
Then what do you want?
ثم ماذا تريد؟
I'll give you everything.
سأعطيك كل شيء.
Everything!
كل شئ!
Mother...
الأم...
I can finally avenge you.
أستطيع أن أنتقم لك أخيرا.
Unless you die,
ما لم تموت،
my wife and child will never
زوجتي وطفلي لن يفعلوا ذلك أبدًا
be safe.
كن آمنا.
Brother.
أخ.
Mother.
الأم.
Pei Ji!
باي جي!
Pei Ji, open the door!
بي جي، افتح الباب!
Pei Ji.
باي جي.
Pei Ji!
باي جي!
Summon the physician.
استدعاء الطبيب.
Hurry, get the physician!
اسرعوا واحضروا الطبيب!
Why risk yourself alone?
لماذا تخاطر بنفسك وحدك؟
Didn't we agree
ألم نتفق؟
to wait at the villa
الانتظار في الفيلا
for your return
لعودتك
and you'll bring us home?
وستعيدنا إلى المنزل؟
So this is the moment
إذن هذه هي اللحظة
you finally show urgency.
أنت تظهر أخيرا الاستعجال.
For me?
لي؟
We're both sorrowful souls.
نحن الاثنان أرواح حزينة.
I understand
أفهم
your burdens.
أعبائك.
At dusk,
عند الغسق،
I'd often watch from the study window
كنت أشاهد في كثير من الأحيان من نافذة الدراسة
as you sat
كما جلست
beneath Mandala blooms,
تحت أزهار الماندالا،
gazing at the waterside pavilion.
التحديق في جناح واجهة الماء.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
did you ever think of me?
هل فكرت بي يوما؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
Thought about how to use me?
فكرت في كيفية استخدامي؟
At first, yes.
في البداية، نعم.
But later, not anymore.
ولكن في وقت لاحق، ليس بعد الآن.
When did it change?
متى تغيرت؟
After you gave me Qin Xiaoniang's needle pouch.
بعدما أعطيتني حقيبة إبرة تشين شياونيانغ.
♪A floating dream, yet all we see is the human scene♪
♪ حلم عائم، ولكن كل ما نراه هو المشهد الإنساني ♪
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Three years ago.
منذ ثلاث سنوات.
I should have come to you three years earlier.
كان ينبغي لي أن آتي إليك قبل ثلاث سنوات.
♪- Unmoved by the sorrow - I still linger♪
♪- لا أتأثر بالحزن - ما زلت أتردد♪
♪Love and hate entangle, not only in the past♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، ليس فقط في الماضي♪
♪The past blinds me, gone in a moment♪
♪الماضي يعميني، ذهب في لحظة♪
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
I might not have been able to protect you.
ربما لم أتمكن من حمايتك.
♪- Moon-bright heart, dust never clings - Bound with you♪
♪- قلب مشرق كالقمر، الغبار لا يلتصق أبدًا - مرتبط بك♪
It was you
لقد كنت انت
who saved me and Zhao.
الذي أنقذني وتشاو.
This time,
هذه المرة،
you've won against me.
لقد فزت ضدي.
Next time,
المرة التالية،
we won't need schemes.
لن نحتاج إلى مخططات.
No more cautious steps.
لا مزيد من الخطوات الحذرة.
We'll be an ordinary couple.
سوف نكون زوجين عاديين.
What do you mean by "next time"?
ماذا تقصد ب "المرة القادمة"؟
♪Through the crowd, a searing glance♪
♪من خلال الحشد، نظرة حارقة♪
♪Oft I come and turn♪
♪في كثير من الأحيان آتي وأتحول♪
♪Oft I go and return♪
♪في كثير من الأحيان أذهب وأعود♪
♪Too scared to stay♪
♪خائف جدًا من البقاء♪
♪She gazes at the bright moon above♪
♪تنظر إلى القمر الساطع في الأعلى♪
♪While I fall through mountains♪
♪بينما أسقط من خلال الجبال♪
♪Guarding this shattered world♪
♪حراسة هذا العالم المحطم♪
Next time...
المرة التالية...
♪Love and hate entangle, not only in the past♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، ليس فقط في الماضي♪
♪The past blinds me, gone in a moment♪
♪الماضي يعميني، ذهب في لحظة♪
No.
لا.
No!
لا!
♪This dream, serene delight♪
♪هذا الحلم، متعة هادئة♪
♪I once fell into deep love♪
♪لقد وقعت في حب عميق ذات مرة♪
♪Caught in a drama of love and hate♪
♪وقعت في دراما الحب والكراهية♪
♪Trapped in self-made cages♪
♪محاصرون في أقفاص من صنعهم♪
♪To whom should I direct my questions♪
♪إلى من أوجه أسئلتي♪
♪Heal my wounds from past dreams♪
♪ شفاء جروحي من أحلام الماضي ♪
♪Fate bestowed me both joy and pain♪
♪لقد منحني القدر كل من الفرح والألم♪
♪Left me a kiss of love and hate♪
♪ترك لي قبلة من الحب والكراهية♪
♪Who will unravel my dreams so deep♪
♪من سيكشف أحلامي العميقة؟♪
♪Who will save me from this lonely place♪
♪من سينقذني من هذا المكان الوحيد♪
♪Who will give me back my lonely grace♪
♪من سيعيد لي نعمتي الوحيدة♪
♪I dare not ask the infatuated ones♪
♪لا أجرؤ على سؤال المغرمين♪
♪As the moonlight thickens♪
♪مع ازدياد كثافة ضوء القمر♪
♪What I await♪
♪ما أنتظره♪
♪Which heartless soul♪
♪أي روح بلا قلب♪
♪Love departs, hatred persists♪
♪الحب يرحل، والكراهية تبقى♪
♪I woke too soon to bygone bonds♪
♪استيقظت مبكرًا جدًا على الروابط القديمة♪
♪Forgetting the lost one in old dreams♪
♪نسيان المفقود في الأحلام القديمة♪
♪No longer waiting for estranged souls♪
♪لم يعد هناك انتظار للأرواح المنفصلة♪
♪Memories flow in the deep night♪
♪تتدفق الذكريات في الليل العميق♪
♪Illuminating lonely spirits♪
♪إضاءة الأرواح الوحيدة♪
♪Become an ordinary mortal♪
♪أصبح إنسانًا عاديًا♪
♪Next spring will open heart's doors♪
♪الربيع القادم سيفتح أبواب القلب♪
♪Not seeking a specific beloved♪
♪لا أبحث عن حبيب محدد♪
♪Gracefully embracing affections♪
♪احتضان المشاعر برشاقة♪